Guide to the Tristan Taormino papers, 1989-2014.
Taormino, Tristan papers
- Series V. Projects
  - She Hate Me
    - She Hate Me screenplay with edits, 2003-08-19; Genet, Michael; Lee, Spike (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - She Hate Me contact list, 2003-09-03 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - She Hate Me screenplay 2nd revision, 2003-09-10; Genet, Michael; Lee, Spike (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - She Hate Me crew list, 2003-09-25, 2003-11-18 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - She Hate Me screenplay 2nd revision, 2003-09-29-2003-10-01; Genet, Michael; Lee, Spike (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - She Hate Me screenplay 2nd revision, 2003-09-29-2003-10-03; Genet, Michael; Lee, Spike (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - She Hate Me cast list, 2003-10-01 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - She Hate Me publicity tour, 2004-05-13-2004-06-21 (Box 10, Folder 23)
      Includes correspondence, tour schedules, plane boarding passes
    - What My Queer Eye Sees in She Hate Me, 2004-05-21; Taormino, Tristan (Box 10, Folder 24)
      She Hate Me public relations piece
    - Invitation to world premiere of She Hate Me, 2004-07-20 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Dark Odyssey
    - Dark Odyssey: 101, 2003-2010 (Box 14, Folder 8)
      Includes orientation material
    - Dark Odyssey: Staff, 2003-2010 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Dark Odyssey: Miscellaneous, 2003-2010 (Box 14, Folder 10)
      Includes directions to event locations, pamphlets, draft partnership agreement between Tristan and co-founder
    - Dark Odyssey: Summer Camp 2003, 2003-09-11-2003-09-15 (Box 14, Folder 11)
      Includes programs
    - Dark Odyssey: Summer Camp 2004, 2004-09-15-2004-09-20 (Box 14, Folder 12)
      Includes program, quarter cards, weekend schedule
    - Dark Odyssey: Cabins, 2005-2007 (Box 14, Folder 13)
      Includes cabin assignments and information
    - Dark Odyssey: Vendors, 2005-02-2007-09 (Box 14, Folder 14)
      Includes invoices
    - Dark Odyssey Winter Fire 2005, 2005-02-25-2006-02-28 (Box 14, Folder 15)
      Includes program, schedule, local news articles about event, presenter information, general information, quarter cards
    - Dark Odyssey: Summer Camp 2005, 2005-09-14-2005-09-19 (Box 14, Folder 16)
      Includes presenter information
    - Dark Odyssey: Winter Fire 2005/2006, 2005-12-30-2006-01-02 (Box 14, Folder 17)
      Includes quarter cards, program, presenter information
    - Dark Odyssey: Summer Camp 2006, 2006-09 (Box 14, Folder 18)
      Includes programs, camper award ballot
    - Dark Odyssey: Spring Fire 2007, 2007-04-06-2007-04-08 (Box 14, Folder 19)
      Includes programs and weekend schedule
    - Dark Odyssey: Summer Camp 2007, 2007-09-12-2007-09-17 (Box 14, Folder 20)
      Includes programs, camper award ballot, schedule, quarter cards, presenter information, cabin notes, attendee feedback
    - Dark Odyssey 2007 Disk 1, 2007-09-12-2007-09-17; CD-3457; Hollis, Ahren (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Dark Odyssey 2007 Disk 2, 2007-09-12-2007-09-17; CD-3458; Hollis, Ahren (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Dark Odyssey: Winter Fire 2008, 2008-03-21-2008-03-24 (Box 14, Folder 21)
      Includes programs, schedules, maps, general information, quarter cards
    - Dark Odyssey: Summer Camp 2008, 2008-09-11-2008-09-15 (Box 14, Folder 22)
      Includes notes on awards, quarter cards, schedule, programs
    - Dark Odyssey: Summer Camp 2008, 2008-09-11-2008-09-15; CD-3459; Wolf, Ahren (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Dark Odyssey: Winter Fire 2009, 2009-02-13-2009-02-15 (Box 14, Folder 23)
      Includes programs, schedule, map
    - Dark Odyssey: Summer Camp 2009, 2009-09-16-2009-09-21 (Box 14, Folder 24)
      Includes programs, cabin information, schedule, camper award ballot, attendee evaluations
    - Dark Odyssey: Summer Camp 2009, 2009-09-16-2009-09-21; CD-3460; Morgan, Steve (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Dark Odyssey: Summer Camp 2009, 2009-09-16-2009-09-21; CD-3461; Hypnox (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Dark Odyssey: Winter Fire 2010, 2010-02-26-2010-02-28 (Box 14, Folder 25)
      Includes program, quarter card, door signs
    - Dark Odyssey: Summer Camp 2010, 2010-09-15-2010-09-20 (Box 14, Folder 26)
      Includes programs, expense report, badge information
    - Dark Odyseey: Legal, 2011-2012 (Box 14, Folder 27)
      Includes expense report
- Series VI. Correspondence
  - Fan Mail
    - Fan mail, 1997-12-1999-12 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Other Sales '02, 1999-2006 (Box 12, Folder 6)
      Correspondence requesting merchandise
    - Fan mail, 2000-01-2000-10 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Fan mail, 2000-09-2002-11 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Fan mail, 2001-01-2001-03 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Fan mail, 2001-04-2001-07 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Fan mail, 2001-08 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Fan mail, 2001-09 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Fan mail, 2009-10 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Fan mail, 2001-11-01-2001-12-30 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Fan mail, 2002-01-01-2002-03-31 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Fan mail, 2002-04-2004-08 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Fan mail, 2003-2006 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Fan mail, 2006-06-2008-02 (Box 19, Folder 13)
      Includes 3 DVDs of Nick Roe's writing
    - The Voice, Date Unknown; DVD-2153; Roe, Nick (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - The Third Date Preparation, Date Unknown; DVD-2154; Roe, Nick (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - The Third Date Revised, Date Unknown; DVD-2155; Roe, Nick (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Anal Advisor
    - Taboo Letters Done, 1999-09-2002-02 (Box 12, Folder 1)
      Fan mail from Hustler’s Taboo “Anal Advisor” column - monthly then bimonthly column; people sent questions to a PO Box.
    - Letters: Anal Advisor 1, 2000-2002, 2014 (Box 12, Folder 2)
      Originally in a binder; sections include: Anatomy, Cum in ass, Enema, Erection, 1st Time
    - Letters: Anal Advisor 1, 2000-2002 (Box 12, Folder 3)
      Originally in a binder; sections include: Fisting, Follow, Health, Long Term, Lube
    - Letters: Anal Advisor 2, 2000-2002 (Box 12, Folder 4)
      Originally in a binder; sections include: Men Pleasure, Miscellaneous, Pain, Penetration, Poop Urge
    - Letters: Anal Advisor 2, 2000-2002 (Box 12, Folder 5)
      Originally in a binder; sections include: Psychology, Rimming, Safe/STD, Search, Toys, Toys Big, Vids/BKS, Women Pleasure
    - Ask Tristan - In, 2000-01-2002-06 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Series VII. Assorted Materials
  - Sketch by fan, Undated; Kindley, Wayne (Box 7, Folder 6)
    Drawing of Taormino made by and given to her by fan
  - Three religious dildos, Undated; MU-1771-1773 (Box 18)
  - Homosexuality in Perspective, Undated; Masters, William H.; Johnson, Virginia E. (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - How to Shave, Undated; Anderson, J T (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Four Prose Poems, Undated (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Vivid Ed Toy Line, Undated (Box 12, Folder 18)
    Includes sketches of potenial toys
  - New Century Network, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - New Century Network NewsWorks, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Adult industry general, 1998-2009 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    Includes signed photos of actors
  - "BITCH" materials, 1998-10 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Large contact sheet from photo shoot that led to the performance “BITCH” at a bar in NYC, along with quarter card advertising the event
  - Playthings poster, 1999 (Mapcase-folder 2)
    Signed by Andrew Blake
    Blake, Andrew; Studio A Entertainment
  - Good Vibrations catalogues, 1999-03-2001-08 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Academic work of others, 1999-11-2014 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Papers discussing Tristan Taormino's work and influence
  - Miscellaneous clips, 2000-08-2002-03 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Legal, 2001-04-30, 2004-05-25-2004-11 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Includes Taormino's deposition for Barbara Mitke and the National Coalition for Sexual Freedom vs. John Ashcroft, Attorney General of the United States of America, and the United States of America
  - Sweet Boy, 2001; V-9815; Everett, Karen (Box 8)
    Produced and directed by Karen Everett
  - U.S. ephemera, 2001-2011 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Non U.S. ephemera, 2004-2009 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - VCA Pictures poster, 2005 (Mapcase-folder 2)
    Signed by Eon McKai
    McKai, Eon; VCA Pictures
  - Joanna's Angels 2 Alt Throttle poster, 2006 (Mapcase-folder 2)
    Signed by Joanna Angel
    Angel, Joanna; VCA Pictures
  - Shevibe: The Rise of Reason poster, 2013-07 (Mapcase-folder 2)
    SV No. 5; Taormino as a superhero "Shevibe"
  - SAFE SEX BANG exhibition catalog, 2013-11-08-2014-01-31 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    SAFE SEX BANG: The Buzz Bense Collection of Safe Sex Posters
  - Unlocked Calendar, 2014 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    Created by students at Wesleyan University
  - Sex toy catalogues, Date Unknown (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Sex toy instructions, Date Unknown (Box 12, Folder 23)
SEPARATED MATERIAL
Books by Tristan Taormino - cataloged individually in the Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections
Taormino, Tristan. Dressing up and fleshing out: butch/femme erotics and politics all tied up, 1993
Taormino, Tristan. New sex: dirty secrets for maximum pleasure, 2001
Taormino, Tristan. Ekstase pur: die ErfuÌˆllung Ihrer sexuellen WuÌˆnsche, 2002
Taormino, Tristan. Tout savoir sur le plaisir anal: (pour elle), 2005
Taormino, Tristan. Opening Up: A Guide to Creating and Sustaining Open Relationships, 2008
Taormino, Tristan. Sekstoys: van vibrators en dildo's tot schommels en slings, speelse en kinky slaapkameraccessoires voor een geweldig seksleven, 2010
Taormino, Tristan. Plaisir anal sur toutes les formes: un guide pour elle et lui, 2010
Sexuality Publications Collected by Tristan Taormino - cataloged individually in the Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections
Quarter Link, 1992-02, Vol. 6 No. 1
Loving More, 2002-09-2002-11, No. 31
Loving More, 2002-12-2003-02, No. 32
Sticky, 2004-12, No. 1, Eros Comix
Sticky, 2005-02, No. 2, Eros Comix
Housewives at Play: Sugar & Spice, 2005-10, Eros Comix
Loving More, 2006-12-2007-02, No. 37
Best of Pin Curl, 2011
Salacious, 2011, No. 1
Salacious, 2011, No. 2
Salacious, 2011, No. 4
Unlocked, 2013-03-2013-05, Vol. 5 Issue 1
The Advocate, 1991-11-05
The Advocate, 1992-01-14
The Advocate, 1992-10-06
The Advocate, 1992-11-17
The Advocate, 1994-04-19
The Advocate, 1994-11-15
The Advocate, 1994-12-13
The Advocate, 1995-03-21
The Advocate, 1996-04-16
The Advocate, 1996-06-25
The Advocate, 1996-07-23
The Advocate, 1996-08-20
The Advocate, 1997-10-14
The Advocate, 2000-04-25
The Advocate, 2000-04-30
The Leatherfolk Connection, 1991-09-1991-11
The Leatherfolk Connection, 1991-12-1992-02
Bennett, George. Mannequins, 1977
Bennett, George. Mannequins, 1977
Winks, Cathy. New Good Vibrations guide to sex, 1997
Girl's guide to taking over the world: writings from the girl zine revolution, 1997
You are being lied to: the disinformation guide to media distortion, historical whitewashes and cultural myths, 2001
Black book, 1992
Volcano, Del Lagrace. Sublime mutations, 2000
Kloster, Doris. Forms of desire, 1998
Bomb, Irvin. Art of Irvin Bomb, 2001
Swan, Rebecca. Assume nothing, 2004
Gauthier, Isabelle. Hot pants: do it yourself gynecology, herbal remedies, 2013
Spirit captured: the official photojournal of Celebration '90--Gay Games III & Cultural Festival, 1990
Bailey, Sarah E. Truth about infidelity: hypocrisy finally revealed!, 2005
Pervert: the Art Gallery, University of California, Irvine, 1995
Everything you know about sex is wrong: the Disinformation guide to the extremes of human sexuality (and everything in between), 2006
Rosen, Michael A. Sexual portraits: photographs of radical sexuality, 1990
KloÌˆs, Bodo W. Skizzenbuch, 1999
Garoutte, Claire. Matter of trust = Sache des Vertrauens, 1996
Stillman, Matthew. Genesis deflowered, 2013
Lehermitte, Christian. Agenda 1994, 1993, Rare spiral bound book of kinky photography, Captive Liberation